She's coming for you
The Stolen is a western, action, adventure film directed by Niall Johnson.
The story of a woman who must find her kidnapped son, navigating a world she
doesn't know, on the edge of danger with every heartbeat.
Charlotte Lockton, played by Alice Eve.
Joshua McCullen, played by Jack Davenport.
Bully, played by Graham McTavish.
Mr. Russell, played by Richard O'Brien.
Hunter, played by Cohen Holloway.
Bandit, played by Glen Levy.
Prayers for the Stolen (Spanish: Noche de fuego, lit.
'Night of Fire') is a 2021 Mexican drama film directed and written by Tatiana
Huezo, which adapts Jennifer Clement's novel Prayers for the Stolen.
The tone is emotional.